Guide to the Intercollegiate Center for Nursing Education Director (Hilda Boerhave Roberts) Papers 1924-2001
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Intercollegiate Center for Nursing Education (ICNE), Series 3
  - ICNE Administration Faculty Correspondence with various Washington State Hospitals - 1970 (Folder 17)
  - ICNE Administration Faculty Development Day - 1973 to 1975 (Folder 18)
  - ICNE Administration Faculty Handbook - 1969 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Administration Faculty Handbook - 1970 to 1971 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Administration Faculty Handbook - Summer, 1971 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Administration Faculty Handbook - 1972 to 1973 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Administration Faculty Handbook - 1974 to 1975 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Administration Faculty Handbook - 1975 to 1976 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Administration Faculty Handbook - 1980 to 1981 (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Administration Faculty Handbook - 1981 to 1982 (Folder 8)
  - ICNE Administration Faculty Reference and Procedures Manual - 1967 to 1974 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Administration Faculty Rosters and Teaching Assignments - 1969 to 1982 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Administration Faculty Sabbatical Interviews - 1960s to 1970s (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Administration New Faculty Orientation, Surveys and Correspondence - 1966 to 1978 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Administration Nursing Student Rosters - 1967 to 1978 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Administration, Personnel, and Faculty Appointments; Newspaper Articles - 1950 to 1982 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Administration Personnel Changes and New Appointments Correspondence - 1965 to 1982 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Administration Registered Nurse Mailing Lists - 1960s to 1980s (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Administration Search Committee for a Nursing Advisor Materials and Correspondence - 1980 to 1982 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Administration Search Committee for a Dean of Nursing, Correspondence - 1967 to 1981 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Administration Search Committee for a Dean of Nursing, Materials - 1975 to 1981 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Administration Search Committee for a Dean of Nursing, Minutes - 1981 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Administration Search Committee for a Dean of Nursing "Search Committee File" - 1981 to 1982 (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Administration Staff Development Activities - 1972 to 1973 (Folder 8)
  - ICNE Administration "Work Week" Workshops - 1973 (Folder 9)
  - ICNE Admissions Application and Instructions - 1969 to 1982 (Folder 10)
  - ICNE Admissions Binder - 1971 to 1974 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Admissions Correspondence with Prospective Students - 1965 to 1987 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Admissions List of Prospective Students at Other Institutions - 1969 to 1982 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Admissions Lists of Students Accepted to Center - 1969 to 1981 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Admissions Policies, Procedures, and Criteria - 1969 to 1991 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Admissions Policies, Procedures, and Criteria; Faculty Correspondence - 1969 to 1982 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Biennial Budget 1967-1969 Materials and Correspondence (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Biennial Budget 1969-1971 Correspondence (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Biennial Budget 1969-1971 Materials (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Biennial Budget 1971-1973 Correspondence (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Biennial Budget 1971-1973 Materials (1 of 2) (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Biennial Budget 1971-1973 Materials (2 of 2) (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Biennial Budget 1973-1975 Correspondence (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Biennial Budget 1973-1975 Materials (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Biennial Budget 1975-1977, Materials and Correspondence (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Biennial Budget 1977-1979 Materials and Correspondence (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Biennial Budget 1979-1981 Materials and Correspondence (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Biennial Budget 1981-1983 Materials and Correspondence (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Biennial Budget 1983-1985 Materials and Correspondence (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Biannual Budget Materials and Correspondence - 1985 to 1988 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Budget Departmental Budget Summary - 1967 to 1980 (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Budget Newspaper Articles - 1964 to 1987 (Folder 8)
  - ICNE Continuing Education Program Correspondence with Other Institutions on Developing Program - 1965 to 1974 (Folder 9)
  - ICNE Continuing Education Program Correspondence with Prospective Students - 1965 to 1980 (Folder 10)
  - ICNE Continuing Education Program Correspondence with WSU Administration - 1966 to 1981 (Folder 11)
  - ICNE Continuing Education Program Course Offerings - 1966 to 1991 (Folder 12)
  - ICNE Continuing Education Program Development, Materials, and Research - 1966 to 1989 (Folder 13)
  - ICNE Continuing Education Program Hilda B. Roberts Notes - 1970s (Folder 14)
  - ICNE Continuing Education Program Meetings with Washington State Department of Social and Health Services - 1966 to 1072 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Continuing Education Program Newspaper Articles - 1960s to 1975 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Continuing Education Program: Refresher and Short Course Outlines and Materials - 1951 to 1969 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Continuing Education Program Workshop "Legal Aspects of Nursing" - 1967 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Continuing Education Program Workshop "Meeting the New Challenges of Nursing Education" - 1989 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Continuing Education Program Workshop "Nursing Theory: Its Application in Practice" - 1980 to 1983 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Continuing Education Program Workshop: "Reality Shock" - 1978 (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Continuing Education Program: Workshops, Short and Refresher Course Brochures - 1966 to 1988 (Folder 8)
  - ICNE Development Agreement and Revisions to Establish a Center for Nursing Education in Spokane - 1968 to 1974 (Folder 9)
  - ICNE Development Agreements with Spokane Area Medical Facilities for Use in Nursing Education - 1966 to 1971 (Folder 10)
  - ICNE Development Application to Establish a School of Nursing Submitted to Washington State Board of Nursing - 1969 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Development Correspondence with Other Institutions on ICNE Program - 1963 to 1976 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Development Eastern Washington State College Documents and Correspondence - 1965 to 1974 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Development Fort Wright College Documents and Correspondence - 1967 to 1982 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Development Grant Projects "Active Grants Binder" - 1971 to 1972 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Development Grant Projects: "Construction Grant" for Holy Family Facility - 1971 to 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Development Grant Projects Construction Grant for ICNE Center - 1971 to 1975 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Development Grant Projects Construction Grant for ICNE Center - 1975 to 1978 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Development Grant Projects "Curriculum Grant" Applications and Materials - 1971 to 1976 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Development Grant Project "Expanding and Strengthening a Baccalaureate Nursing Program Conducted in Spokane, Washington"--Applications and Materials - 1969 to 1972 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Development Grant Project "Expanding and Strengthening a Baccalaureate Nursing Program Conducted in Spokane, Washington"--Final Report - 1976 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Development Grant Project "Expanding and Strengthening a Baccalaureate Nursing Program Conducted in Spokane, Washington"--Proposals and Drafts - 1970s (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Development Grant Projects Financial Distress Grant Materials and Correspondence - 1971 to 1972 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Development Grant Projects Financial Distress Grant Materials and Correspondence - 1972 to 1974 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Development Grant Projects "Financial Distress Grant" Materials and Correspondence - 1975 to 1976 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Development Grant Projects "Health, Education, and Welfare Division of Nursing Training Grant' Materials and Correspondence - 1966 to 1972 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Development Grant Projects Information and Instructions - 1964 to 1975 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Development Grant Projects Materials and Information and Nurse Training Act - 1964 to 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Development Grant Projects "Medical Library Resource Grant" Materials and Correspondence - 1968 to 1969 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Development Grant Projects " Newspaper Articles" - 1971 to 1987 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Development Grant Projects "Nursing Capitation Grants" Applications and Materials - 1972 to 1977 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Development Grant Projects "Nursing Capitation Grants" Correspondence - 1969 to 1981 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Development Grant Projects Research Project Proposals - 1966 to 1975 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Development Grant Projects Schedules and Progress Reports - 1966 to 1972 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Development Joint Committee on Nursing Education Plans and Proposals for Spokane Center - 1965 to 1970 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Development Newspaper Articles - 1956 to 1989 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Development Notes and Materials Collected by Hilda B. Roberts - 1960s to 1970s (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Development Petition to Establish Baccalaureate Nursing Program - 1968 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Development Photograph Slides "Dedication of Building" - 1980 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Development Proposal for Two-Year Preprofessional Nursing Program with WSU and University of Washington - 1964 to 1965 (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Development Proposal for Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education Funds to Study Feasibility of ICNE - 1966 (Folder 8)
  - ICNE Development Reference Materials on Graduate Nursing Education in Spokane, WA - 1935 to 1981 (Folder 9)
  - ICNE Development Report "A Baccalaureate Program in Eastern Washington" by Hilda B. Roberts - 1967 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Development Report--Annual report to the United States Department of Health and Human Services - 1980 to 1982 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Development Report "Community Planning For Baccalaureate Nursing Education in Eastern Washington" by Hilda B. Roberts - 1964 to 1968 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Development Report Comprehensive Report on Establishment of ICNE - 1960s (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Development Report Progress Reports to Washington State Board of Nursing - 1971 to 1974 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Development Report "Self-Evaluation Accreditation Report" for National League for Nursing - 1974 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Development Report "Self Study Report for the National League for Nursing" - 1969 to 1980 (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Development Report "The Need for a Baccalaureate-Degree in Nursing at Washington State University" by Hilda B. Roberts (Folder 8)
  - ICNE Development Report "The Need to Increase the Nurse Supply and the Crisis in Nursing" by Hilda B. Roberts, Notes/Drafts (Folder 9)
  - ICNE Development Report "The Ten Year Plan for Nursing Education at Washington State University" - 1967 to 1977 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Development Report "Toward Quality in Nursing-Needs and Goals" - 1963 to 1970 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Development Report to Washington State Board of Nursing on Plan for Development of Nursing Center - 1969 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Development Reports for Council on Higher Education in Washington - 1969 to 1971 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Development Reports on Clinical Facilities in Spokane, Materials and Hilda B. Roberts Notes - 1966 to 1967 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Development WSU Documents and Correspondence - 1964 to 1971 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Development Whitworth College Documents and Correspondence - 1965 to 1980 (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Library Collections, Acquisitions, and Inventories - 1960s to 1970s (Folder 8)
  - ICNE Library Correspondence - 1970 to 1980 (Folder 9)
  - ICNE Library Hilda B. Roberts Notes and Drafts - 1970s (Folder 10)
  - ICNE Library Information and Evaluations - 1970 to 1972 (Folder 11)
  - ICNE Materials for the Historical Collection - 1960s to 1990s (Folder 12)
  - ICNE Negotiations for Educational and Clinical Facilities at Sacred Heart Hospital in Spokane - 1968 (Folder 13)
  - ICNE Minority Program in Nursing Materials - 1972 to 1982 (Folder 14)
  - ICNE Nursing Advisor Assignments, Interview Materials, and Correspondence - 1968 to 1982 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Curriculum Changes and Course Outlines - 1964 to 1976 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Curriculum and Program Development Workshops - 1968 to 1972 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Curriculum and Program Development Workshops - 1973 to 1980 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Curriculum and Program Development Workshops--Surveys and Evaluations - 1970 to 1972 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Curriculum "Course Outline Workshops" - 1973 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Curriculum Development "Curriculum Revision Materials" - 1969 to 1973 (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Curriculum Development Faculty Correspondence - 1963 to 1982 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Curriculum Development Notes and Materials by Hilda B. Roberts - 1973 to 1982 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Curriculum Development Packet - 1973 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Curriculum Development Packet - 1977 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Curriculum Development Packet - 1978 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Curriculum Development Packet - 1981 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Curriculum Development Progress - 1975 to 1979 (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Curriculum Development Resources and Research Materials - 1930s to 1970s (Folder 8)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Curriculum Development Workshop "Curriculum Days" Correspondence and Materials - 1975 to 1979 (Folder 9)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Curriculum Requirements and Course Descriptions - 1960 to 1981 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Newspaper Articles - 1965 to 1989 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Pamphlets and Brochures - 1969 to 1992 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Pamphlets and Brochures - 1991 to 2000 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Philosophy Drafts and Revisions - 1968 to 1975 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Purpose and Objectives Drafts and Revisions - 1966 to 1976 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Philosophies and Objectives Sample Statements - 1950 to 1968 (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Process Workshop - 1972 (Folder 8)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Report Comparing Center Student GPA with Campus GPA, By Robert Irwin - 1974 (Folder 9)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Statements and Descriptions - 1968 to 1982 (Folder 10)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Surveys and Questionnaires - 1964 to 1981 (Folder 11)
  - ICNE Nursing Program Terminal Behavior Objectives Workshop - 1972 (Folder 12)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities and Construction Newspaper Articles - 1973 to 1982 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center ADT Alarm System Correspondence - 1979 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center Architectural Project Manual, Preliminary Draft - 1978 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center "Art Selection" - 1979 to 1982 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center "Building Correspondence - 1976 to 1982 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center Building Proposals - 1979 to 1981 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center "Building Funds" Materials and Correspondence - 1976 to 1979 (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center Building Plans - 1970s (Folder 8)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center Building Profile and Aerial Drawings - 1978 to 1980 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center Building Publicity and Newspaper Articles - 1976 to 1982 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center Classroom Dimensions (Chairs)(A-V Facilities) Photographs and Materials - 1980 to 1981 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center Construction and Planning Manual - 1976 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center Construction Project: Phase II - 1977 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center Dedication Ceremony and Plaque - 1979 to 1980 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center Draft Application for Construction Funds - 1975 to 1978 (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center "El-Wagner A-V Installation" - 1978 to 1981 (Folder 8)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center Emergency Escape Routes and Plans - 1970s (Folder 9)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center Entrance Sign - 1980 (Folder 10)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center "Environmental Assessment" for Construction of ICNE - 1976 (Folder 11)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center Equipment Inventory - 1979 to 1982 (Folder 12)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center Equipment--Movable - 1978 to 1980 (Folder 13)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center Final Contractor Building Survey Correspondence - 1981 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center Functional Layouts - 1970s (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center Keys Correspondence and Materials - 1979 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center "Landscaping" - 1978 to 1982 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center Post Bid Construction Activity Materials and Correspondence - 1976 to 1980 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center "Post Occupancy Evaluations" - 1980 to 1981 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center "Punch Lists" for Center Repairs - 1980 to 1981 (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center "Response to Brugger LTR" - 1978 to 1979 (Folder 8)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center "Room Signage" Documents - 1980 (Folder 9)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center Schematics - 1976 (Folder 10)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Center Telephone Data for ICNE - 1977 to 1982 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities "Environmental Impact Statement for Westwood Apartment Complex, Spokane" - 1977 to 1980 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities "History Project" on Building at ICNE - 1968 to 1982 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities "Holy Family Facility" as Possible ICNE Site - 1974 to 1977 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities Minor Capital Outlay Needs - 1969 to 1982 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Physical Facilities--Remodeling and Space Considerations, Plans - 1967 to 1982 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Policies and Procedures for Student Admissions and Grading - 1970 to 1980 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Policies and Procedures for Nursing Aides and Other Student Employees - 1969 to 1981 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Property Inventories and Acquisitions - 1968 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Publication "Alumni Newsletter" - 1975 to 1987 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Publication "Center Focus" Newsletter - 1985 to 1999 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Publication "Inside the ICNE" Newsletter - 1976 to 1979 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Publication "Inside the ICNE" Newsletter - 1980 to 1983 (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Publication "Research news and Views" Newsletter - 1987 to 1991 (Folder 8)
  - ICNE Publication "Pains" Newsletter - 1973 to 1981 (Folder 9)
  - ICNE Registered Nurse Outreach Program Admissions Enrollment - 1964 to 1981 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Registered Nurse Outreach Program Correspondence with Faculty - 1977 to 1982 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Registered Nurse Outreach Program Correspondence with Students and Nurses - 1977 to 1981 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Registered Nurse Outreach Program Faculty Itineraries and Travel Documents - 1970 to 1982 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Registered Nurse Outreach Program Hilda B. Roberts Notes - 1977 to 1982 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Registered Nurse Outreach Program Materials - 1976 to 1980 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Registered Nurse Outreach Program Tri-Cities Site Schedules and Materials - 1977 to 1982 (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Registered Nurse Outreach Program Walla Walla Site Schedules and Materials - 1976 to 1982 (Folder 8)
  - ICNE Registered Nurse Outreach Program Wenatchee Site Schedules and Materials - 1977 to 1982 (Folder 9)
  - ICNE Registered Nurse Outreach Program Yakima Site Schedules and Materials - 1977 to 1982 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Registration Complete Nursing Student Rosters - 1977 to 1983 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Registration Enrollment Data, Projections, and Census Reports - 1964 to 1987 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Registration Faculty Correspondence on Enrollment - 1971 to 1980 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Registration Instructions, Materials, and Correspondence - 1969 to 1981 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Registration Lists of Students Enrolled in Coursework - 1970 to 1981 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Registration Nursing Student Class Rosters - 1970 to 1980 (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Registration--Nursing Student Textbook Lists - 1970s (Folder 8)
  - ICNE Report "Educational Interests of Registered Nurses in Eastern Washington" - 1975 (Folder 9)
  - ICNE Report "How Students Learn and Are Motivated" - 1970 (Folder 10)
  - ICNE Transfer Program in Nursing College Visitation and Correspondence - 196 to 1983 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Transfer Program in Nursing Correspondence with University of Oregon Nursing Faculty - 1962 to 1971 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Transfer Program in Nursing Information and Materials - 196 to 1982 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Transfer Program in Nursing Report on Cooperative Program Between WSU and University of Idaho - 1976 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Transfer Program in Nursing Report on Transfer Student Process by Hilda B. Roberts - 1968 (Folder 5)
  - Washington State and Federal Laws Regarding Nurses - 1939 to 1986 (Folder 6)
  - WSU Conference "Expression of Sexuality" at WSU, Materials and Correspondence - 1973 (Folder 7)
  - WSU Dissertation "A Comparison of Baccalaureate and Associate Degree Nursing Students on Selected Personality Characteristics" - 1971 (Folder 8)
  - WSU Multi-Purpose Communication System and "two-way television"--Committee Materials, Correspondence, and Hilda B. Roberts Notes - 1969 to 1974 (Folder 9)
  - WSU Division of Sciences Report "The Six Year Planning Goals for the Division of Sciences" - 1980 (Folder 10)
  - WSU Study "Backgrounds and Characteristics of Girls Who Plan to Become Nurses, Teachers, and Secretaries" by Walter Slocum - 1966 (Folder 11)
  - WSU Study "Historical View of Baccalaureate Nursing Education in Spokane Area, 1930-1968" by Jill H. Pendarvis (Folder 12)
  - WSU Study "Study of Performance of Nursing Students" - 1977 (Folder 13)
- Intercollegiate Center for Nursing Education (ICNE)--Faculty Organizations, Series 3A
  - ICNE Ad Hoc Faculty Committee - 1975 to 1981 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Admissions and Academic Standards Committee, Memorandums and Correspondence - 1969 to 1982 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Admissions and Academic Standards Committee, Minutes and Annual Reports - 1969 to 1988 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Advisory Council to the Continuing Education Program in Nursing, Annual Reports and Minutes - 1966 to 1982 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Advisory Council to the Continuing Education Program in Nursing, Correspondence - 1965 to 1967 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Building Committee Minutes, Materials, and Correspondence - 1976 to 1981 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Bylaws Committee Minutes and Annual Reports - 1975 to 1981 (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Committee on the Here and Now Curriculum - 1973 (Folder 8)
  - ICNE Continuing Education Committee, Minutes and Correspondence - 1968 to 1974 (Folder 9)
  - ICNE Coordinating Administrative Council Binder - 1972 to 1973 (Folder 10)
  - ICNE Coordinating Administrative Council Correspondence - 1971 to 1973 (Folder 11)
  - ICNE Coordinating Administrative Council (formerly Interinstitutional Committee on Nursing)--Minutes and Reports - 1970 to 1973 (Folder 12)
  - ICNE Curriculum Committee Binder - 1973 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Curriculum Committee--Correspondence and Surveys - 1967 to 1981 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Curriculum Committee--Minutes and Reports - 1970 to 1982 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Educational Resources Committee Annual Report - 1969 to 1975 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Enrollment Committee Minutes - 1970 to 1971 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Executive Committee Minutes and Annual Reports - 1973 to 1982 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Faculty and Student Interview Committee Minutes and Memorandums - 1972 (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Faculty Committee Rosters, Schedules, and Correspondence - 1968 to 1982 (Folder 8)
  - ICNE Faculty Development Committee--Reports, Meetings, and Workshops - 1971 to 1982 (Folder 9)
  - ICNE Faculty In-service Education Committee Minutes - 1970 to 1971 (Folder 10)